# **CANDIDATE OVERVIEW**

#### **IDENTITY**

Name : Yan H

Education : • S1 Applied PhisicsElectronics Instrumentation - Universitas In-

donesia

Certification :

Email : yan.hardianto@idstar.co.id

Position : Technical Consultant - IDstar

Level : Expert

Total Experience : 23 Years

Total Projects : 5 Projects

# RELATED SKILLS (Tools/Skills/Languages)

Java Spring MVC : 13 Years 6 Months

Java Spring Boot : 8 Years 1 Month

Oracle : 13 Years 6 Months

PostgreSql : 4 Years 2 Months

php : 1 Year

Powerbuilder : 2 Years

Java Quarkus : 3 Months

gitlab : 1 Year

linux : 10 Years

bitbucket : 3 Months

Jenkins CI/CD : 3 Months

eclipse : 10 Years

visual code : 3 Months

# WORK EXPERIENCES (3 latest work experiences)

Period : June 2022 - Present

Industries : Information & Technology Services

Position : Backend Lead Developer

Period : June 2010 - June 2022

Industries : Information & Technology Services

Position : Technical Manager

Period : June 2008 - June 2010

Industries : Information & Technology Services

Position : Fullstack Developer

## **Notes**

Willing to Work Hybrid (WFO & WFH) Availability immediately

# **Recruitment Summary**



# Yan H

Technical Consultant - IDstar

#### PROFILE STATEMENT

I am an Experienced Software Engineer with over 20 years of working history in the computer software industry. Skilled in Java, HTML, Linux, Database. I am Certified Java Programmer. Currently I as Software Development Manager. I am responsible for Maintain and improve product. I always upgrade my skills. Most recently, i have completed studies in the Professional Data-Focused Engineering program in Data Science from the School of Algorithmic Data Science.

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCES

November 2022 -February 2023

#### LifeCover

Backend Lead Developer

Tools: Java - Quarkus

docker

gitlab and bitbucket

jenkins kafka kogito postgree linux

Job Desc: - Design architecture software

- Create ARB document before develop application/product
- Code review and merge source code from developer
- Distribute task to Developer Team
- Monitoring and evaluate target development

June 2010 -June 2022

#### Musikkamu

**Backend Lead Developer** 

Tools: Java Spring

Oracle

Apache Tomcat

Linux API

Javascript

Job Desc : Maintenance and Develop SMS, WAP, WEB, UMB, DTMF for value added system of

provider telecomunication



**2** 10 April 1975 (48 years old)

yan.hardianto@idstar.co.id

#### PROFICIENCY AND SKILLS

Java Spring MVC |
Java Spring Boot | Oracle |
PostgreSql | php | Powerbuilder |
Java Quarkus | gitlab | linux |
bitbucket | Jenkins CI/CD | eclipse |
visual code |

#### **EDUCATION**

S1 Applied PhisicsElectronics Instrumentation (1993 - 1999) Universitas Indonesia June 2008 -June 2010

# **Content Provider**

Fullstack Developer

Tools : PHP MySql API Linux

Job Desc: Create, maintenance and enhancetelecomunication based application for support value added system provider telco.

April 2006 -January 2008

#### Dana Pension of Tri Putra

Fullstack Developer

Tools: Power Builder

MySql Windows

Job Desc : Develop application for support company as follow:

- :Dana pension, Helpdesk system, interface rfid, hrd application etc

November 1999 -January 2006

### **CMS**

Data Engineer

Tools: Java desktop

eclipse

Job Desc : Controlling and maintenance data real

time from BEJ.

Research, maintenance and development data

business.